OBJECTIVE

I have experience in developing native Android applications and have completed several course projects using various programming languages. I am passionate about taking on challenging and creative full-time work and constantly learning new skills and knowledge to successfully complete assigned tasks.

SKILLS

Programming Language	 Experienced in Kotlin and Java.
	 Have knowledge about Python, JavaScript and C++.
Framework/Platform	Core: Android Development, Android SDK, Android Jetpack, NO. A. Cooking.
	MVVM, Caching.
	 Third-party libraries: RxJava, RxAndroid, Coroutines, Dagger Hilt,
	Retrofit, JWT, Coil, Glide.
	 Cloud/Database: Firebase, MSSQL.
	 Version control: Git (GitHub).
	 Understand OOP and design patterns.
	 Have knowledge about data structure and algorithm.
Others	Web development: Express.js, Spring MVC, Webservice (RESTful
	API, JSON), WebSocket.
	· Soft skills: Independent and teamwork working skills, problem-
	solving, studious, fast learning.
	English: Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023	Dormitory Android Application for Students Developer GitHub: https://github.com/lttrung2001/dormitory Description: App supports students to register for dorm rooms online and track dormitory information. Team size: 1
June 2022 - Mar 2023	Note Pro Android Application (Version 2) Developer GitHub: https://github.com/lttrung2001/note-pro
	 Description: App helps users to take notes with text and images, supports group messaging within note.

June 2022 - Mar 2023

Note Pro API (Version 2)

Developer

· GitHub: https://github.com/lttrung2001/note-pro-api

· Version 1: https://github.com/lttrung2001/note

- · Description: Provides API for Note Pro Android Application.
- · Team size: 2

Team size: 1

- Responsibilities: Write an API for notes and handle group messaging. Support other members with the Firebase service and the implementation of the user API.
- · Version 1: https://github.com/lttrung2001/note-api

EDUCATION

Aug 2019 - NOW Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Majoring in software engineering from the Faculty of Information

Technology GPA: 3.08/4.0

ACTIVITIES

Feb 2022 - Nov 2022 Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Student Research / Host

Description: Research and build web application supports retrieving mobile phone data using Selenium WebDriver from thegioididong.com,

dienmayxanh.com and fptshop.com

SCHOLARSHIPS

Jul 2022 Academic Encouragement Scholarship for Semester 1, 2021

INTERESTS

Learning new technologies. Updating technology news.